Today I'm going
to tell you
some stories about
cats.
So here's your
one-time edition
of Cat News,
depending on how
many hits it
gets.
Yeah!
Over the past
week, we've had
some great cat
material on the
internet.
First off, collective
soul cat,
with over 1
million views on
YouTube.
Now, you might
remember bumping this
track in your
geo-tracker sometime
in the mid
-90s,
but did your
cat ever ride
shotgun and sing
along?
I didn't think
so.
Next is Cat
Sitting Relax.
This one's got
over 4 million
views, and I
think it's pretty
obvious what.
It's a cat
sitting like a
human.
And there's a
translated poem in
the description that
is worth reading.
And finally, can
you imagine anything
better than an
impromptu-trip to
Disney World?
How about getting
to Orlando and
finding a cat
in your suitcase?
Well, according to
WKMG, that's what
happened to Ethel
Mace.
She was packing
up her suitcase
and Ohio to
go to Florida,
and her kitty
named Bob Bob,
climbed inside without
her knowing.
Ethel went to
the airport and
checked her bag,
and when she
got to Disney
World,
she discovered Bob,
soaking wet, and
then she let
the cat out
of the bag.
What a wacky
story!
I'll leave you
with a reminder
to please pick
up your copy
of Dancing With
Cats.
Thank you.